sarsefiling.co.za 2016-05-16

# Untitled Page

| 

####  Privacy Policy

  * SARS eFiling shall take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information of Users and for the purpose of this clause, "personal information" shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000 (PAIA). The PAIA may be downloaded from: http://www.polity.org.za/page.php?rep_id=471 
  * SARS eFiling may electronically collect, store and use the following personal information of Users 
    * name and surname 
    * contact numbers 
    * non-personal browsing habits and click patterns
    * e-mail address 
    * IP address 
    * User selected password
  * SARS eFiling collects, stores and uses the abovementioned information for the following purposes 
    * Communicate requested information to the User 
    * Provide the User with access to restricted pages on this web site; and 
    * to compile non-personal statistical information about browsing habits, click-patterns and access to the SARS eFiling web site 
  * Information detailed above is collected either electronically by using cookies or is provided voluntarily by the User. Users may determine cookie use independently through their browser settings 
  * SARS eFiling may collect, maintain, save, compile, share, disclose and sell any information collected from users, subject to the following provisions 
    * SARS eFiling shall not disclose personal information from Users unless the User consents thereto 
    * SARS eFiling shall disclose information without the User's consent only through due legal process; and
    * SARS eFiling may compile, use and share any information that does not relate to any specific individual 
  * SARS eFiling owns and retains all rights to non-personal statistical information collected and compiled by SARS eFiling 

Please see the complete Terms and Conditions by clicking here.

All information, content and data on SARS websites and associated facilities, including but not limited to software, hyperlinks and databases, is the property of or licensed to SARS and is protected under applicable South African laws. Unauthorised usage of content and/or information is strictly prohibited. No person, business or web site may reproduce this site, contents, information or any portion thereof.
